Connor Gunderson

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Details

810-289-8430

gundydev@gmail.com

Links

<u>Personal Website</u> (https://connorgunderson.vercel.app/)

Skills

Typescript

Node.js

React

Go

HTML & CSS (and preprocessors)

SQL

noSQL

Clustering and Containerization (Docker & k8)

GraphQL

Cloud Solutions (AWS & Azure)

Full Stack Web Architecture (Monolithic & Microservice Hexagonal)

Version control with Git

General IT and Linux

Cloud Computing (AWS & Azure)

CI/CD with Github Actions

Testing

Quality Assurance

Organization Skills

Leadership Skills

Communication Skills

Effective Time Management

Profile

Software Engineer. Typescript, NodeJS, and Go developer working within the web development industry for 3 years. I am comfortable picking up anything related to NodeJS and typescript. Have intermediate Experience with Go. Confident in picking up any tool or language.

Employment History

Software Engineer, RSI Logistics, Lansing, Michigan

SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Worked on and integrated C# GraphQL API into a React.JS application.
- Quality assurance with unit and e2e testing with Jest, React Testing Libarary, and Cypress.
- migrated over 90% of the codebase to typescript and reduced average monthly bugs from 26 to 2.
- Created various forms and grids to display and validate data against user changes.
- Refactored how the company handles various states within the application and reduced bloat and tech debt throughout.
- Introduced proper documentation practices to excel collaboration within the team.
- Refactored various queries and procedures that face our MS SQL db to ensure better performance.
- Improved our CI/CD pipelines connected to github actions for faster builds and check results.
- Worked with thousands of rail related graphtypes and data models for client consumption.
- Worked with various subject matter experts and internal users to create a better user experience and improve semantics within the application

Software Engineer, ProtoJet, Fraser, Michigan

MARCH 2020 - JUNE 2020

- Created SPA for rapid prototype manufacturing quote application.
- Worked with subject matter experts to define business rules and data models for the application.
- Worked with complicated engineering equations and algorithms to calculate quoting costs.
- used prisma/apollo-server for the backend api and db hosted on a PM2 instance within AWS EC2 services.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Media and Information, Michigan State University, Lansing

SEPTEMBER 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2021

Heavy focus on user experience, data management, observation, and application. General IT information and application. Business communication.

References

Erik Gillespie

erik.gillespie@gmail.com